("How to Save a Life")
♪ Step one, you say we need to talk ♪
♪ He walks, you say sit
down, it's just a talk ♪
♪ He smiles politely back at you ♪
♪ You stare politely right on through ♪
♪ Some sort of window to your right ♪
♪ As he goes left, and you stay right ♪
♪ Between the lines of fear and blame ♪
♪ You begin to wonder why you came ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ Let him know that you know best ♪
♪ 'Cause after all, you do know best ♪
♪ Try to slip past his defense ♪
♪ Without granting innocence ♪
♪ Lay down a list of what is wrong ♪
♪ The things you've told him all along ♪
♪ And pray to God he hears you ♪
♪ And I pray to God he hears you ♪
♪ And where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ As he begins to raise his voice ♪
♪ You lower yours and
grant him one last choice ♪
♪ Drive until you lose the road ♪
♪ Or break with the ones you've followed ♪
♪ He will do one of two things ♪
♪ He will admit to everything ♪
♪ Or he'll say he's just not the same ♪
♪ And you'll begin to
wonder why you came ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ How to save a life ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong? ♪
♪ I lost a friend ♪
♪ Somewhere along in the bitterness ♪
♪ And I would have stayed
up with you all night ♪
♪ Had I known how to save a life ♪
♪ How to save a life ♪